webwire.com 2018-11-24

# Privacy Statement – WebWire

Warmtone Corp., Technical Services Provider for WebWire, respects its users’ privacy. We have created this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your business, organizational and or personal information provided to us.

This Privacy Policy applies to information that we obtain in connection with your use of the WebWire website as it concerns your registration as a user of the WebWire service and submission(s) of news releases and press releases to the WebWire service and recipients, including the use of our online fee collection processes.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new policy on our website. Please consult this policy regularly to stay informed of any changes. Your use of our website will constitute your consent to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of information as described in the version of this Privacy Policy then in effect, and is also subject to our Terms of Service . This Privacy Policy was last revised on the date above. 

## Information We May Collect And Retain

You can browse the WebWire website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. If you decide you would like to utilize WebWire’s business, organizational and personal news distribution services, by registering as a user of the WebWire service, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with business, organizational or personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information to the servers that house WebWire located in the United States.

We may collect and store the following personal information: email addresses, physical contact information, telephone numbers, computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic, to and from the site, and ad data among other information, and this data may also include IP addresses and standard web log information.

All on-line data collection as defined above, and billing for our services, will be protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology that encrypts your information during transmission, with details about WebWire obtainable within our Security Certificate, part of SSL technology.

No financial and transactional data such as credit card numbers, are kept by the WebWire service in any way, and our customer contact policies comply with all applicable laws, rules and regulations, including but not limited to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and laws relating to “spam”.

## Use

All business, organizational and or personal data we collect during the registration and submission process to our service will be utilized by WebWire staff as a means to support our customer service efforts which include: customer support you request, process payments, collect fees, resolve disputes, and troubleshoot problems, prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Service. Additionally, we may use the data we collect about our users to customize, measure, and improve our services and our website’s content and layout.

## Our Disclosure of Your Information

In no way does Warmtone Corp., Technical Services Provider for WebWire, sell or offer your data to outside entities for the purpose of solicitation or communications in any way. Your data is our data, and it is kept internal for our efforts only. We may disclose business, organizational and or personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, or protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety.

## Cookies 

We use “cookies” (small files placed on your hard drive) on certain pages of our website to help analyze our web page flow, customize our services, and measure promotional effectiveness. A few important things you should know about cookies are that: 

We offer certain features that are only available through the use of cookies. We use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status.

Most cookies are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of the site.

## Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information

You can see, review and change most of your personal information by logging into your account on the WebWire site. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. 

Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts in order to comply with law, prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Service and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

## Security

Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and industry standard tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from our site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

## Links to Other Sites

Our site may contain links to other Websites (some of which may be in the form of banner ads and other advertisements). Once you click on these links and exit WebWire, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other Websites, and our linking to these Websites does not indicate any endorsement of these Websites or any affiliation with their providers. These other Websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data, and/or solicit personal information from you. You must check the privacy statements of these other Websites to understand their policies for collecting and using such information.

## Our Policy Toward Children

This site is not directed to children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, he or she should contact us WebWire via our “Contact Us” functionality.

## Business Transfers

Warmtone Corp., Technical Services Provider for WebWire, may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. We will use our reasonable efforts to require our successor to continue to protect your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

## Privacy Errors

We strive to update and improve our website and associated services on an ongoing basis. Because certain elements of our site or services may be in testing phase at any particular time, we may not always catch an unintended disruption in our Privacy Policy, despite our efforts to do so. We therefore welcome feedback on any privacy concerns you may have, and on how to improve our services generally. We do not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply. We will not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of the United States. 

## Questions

If you have any questions regarding this policy, please use WebWire’s “Contact Us” functionality at www.webwire.com.
